<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lucia</string>
    <string name="service_description">BLE service for communication with Arduino</string>

    <string name="ble_not_supported">BLE not supported</string>
    <string name="proximity_description">This button will enable the distance sensor. %1$s</string>
    <string name="led_description">This button will turn on the lights on the stick. %1$s</string>
    <string name="beep_description">This button will turn on the beeping feedback from the sensor. %1$s</string>
    <string name="information_description">This button will take you to an information screen.</string>
    <string name="function_on">This function is currently on.</string>
    <string name="function_off">This function is currently off.</string>
    <string name="info_content">Information about the different functions of this application.</string>
    <string name="info_proximity">The proximity sensor will detect objects appearing in front of the
    sensor attached to the cane. The sensor will give feedback in the form of sound or vibration if
    something is detected. Turn the sensor off and on with the button in the top left corner of the
    main screen.</string>
    <string name="info_leds">The light emitting diodes attached to the cane can be turned off and on
    which will make it visible in the dark. Turn this function off and on with the button in the top
    right corner of the main screen. The application will also notify you when it gets dark so that
    you know that you might need to switch on the lights. If the lights are
    on, it will also notify you when it gets bright, so that you know when to switch off the lights in order
    to save battery. </string>
    <string name="info_sound">A beeping sound can be emitted from the phone, indicating when the
    proximity sensor is detecting an object. The interval between beeps will be shorter as the distance
    to the object decreases. Turn this function off and on with the button in the bottom right corner
    of the main screen. When turned off, the feedback will come in the form of vibration, which you will
    sense on the handle of the cane. As with sound, the closer an object, the shorter the vibration
    intervals, and vice versa.</string>
</resources>
